humyo.com 2010-12-29

# Privacy Policy - humyo.com

humyo.com Ltd. ("Humyo") is committed to protecting the privacy of its customers, visitors, users, and others who use www.humyo.com or other web sites owned or operated by Humyo (the "Humyo Sites"). 

This Privacy Notice is incorporated into and is subject to the Humyo Terms of Use. Your use of the Humyo Sites and any personal information you provide on the Humyo Sites remains subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy and the Humyo Terms of Use. 

####  The Information We Collect 

You provide certain personally identifiable information (such as your name and email address) to Humyo when choosing to participate in various activities on the Humyo Sites. 

You may choose to store your electronic files, data and content on the Humyo Sites. 

When you visit the Humyo Sites, we may send one or more cookies - a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters - to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. 

If you choose to purchase services from humyo.com you may provide us with payment information such as credit card details. 

Please note that any video, audio, image, or other content file you choose to share on Humyo becomes published content and is not subject to this Privacy Policy. 

####  How We Use The Information 

If you submit personally identifiable information to us through the Humyo Sites, then we use your personal information to operate, improve, and provide to you the features and functionality of the Humyo Sites. 

If you store your electronic files, data and content on the Humyo Sites, our systems process such data in automated processes for the sole purpose of providing the data storage service to you. We will never look at your stored data without your consent, nor will we ever permit any other person to do so. 

We use cookies to remember your Humyo account information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit and if you have requested your sign in information be stored the next time you visit the Humyo Sites. 

We will not share your personally identifiable information with other, third-party companies for their commercial or marketing use without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. 

We may use your email address without further consent for to contact you for the purposes of maintaining and to notify you of important information relating to your Humyo account. 

Your name may be shared with other humyo users, you may specifiy a screen name or handle as your name. 

If you provide us with payment information such as credit card details we will use it for collecting payment for your order. With the exception of card verification (CVV) numbers, we will store your encrypted payment information in accordance with PCI SSC standards for the purpose of collecting future payments for the services you order. You may opt not to store your payment information on our system and instead to pay charges as they become due. You may remove your payment information from our system at any time and all payment information is automatically purged from our system upon its expiration. 

####  International Users 

The Humyo Sites are hosted in the United Kingdom and are intended for and directed to users in the European Union. If you are a User accessing the Humyo Sites from outside the United Kingdom, through your continued use of the Humyo Sites, which are governed by United Kingdom law, you are transferring your personal information to the United Kingdom and you consent to that transfer. 

####  Merger or Sale 

In the event that Humyo is acquired by or merged with a third party entity, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information we have collected as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. 

####  Changes and updates 

This Privacy Policy may be revised periodically and this will be reflected by the "effective date" below. Please revisit this page to stay aware of any changes. In general, we only use your personal information in the manner described in the Privacy Policy in effect when we received the personal information you provided. Your continued use of the Humyo Sites constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any future revisions. 

####  Date Last Modified 

This Privacy Notice was last modified May 30, 2009. 

####  Contact Information 

Should you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, you should contact us.
